greatcall.com 2019-04-15

# Legal | Privacy Policy | GreatCall

This graphic notice means that you are leaving the GreatCall website and are going to a non-GreatCall website. Please be advised of the following:

  * This external website provides additional information that is consistent with the intended purposes of the GreatCall website; however, the external website is subject to change beyond GreatCall's control.
  * GreatCall cannot attest to the accuracy of a non-GreatCall website.
  * Linking to a non-GreatCall site does not constitute an endorsement by GreatCall or any of its employees of the sponsors or the information and the products presented on the site.
  * You will be subject to the distination site's privacy policy and other terms of use when you follow the link.

###  Privacy Policy 

#####  GreatCall, Inc. Privacy Statement 

GreatCall, Inc. (“GreatCall”) respects your privacy and the privacy of your loved ones, and is committed to protect the personal information that you and they share with us. By using our greatcall.com web site (the “Web site”), you agree that your use of the Web site is governed by this privacy policy and our Terms of Use. This privacy policy shall also apply to your access of our Web site through mobile devices, tablets and through our apps, and your other interactions with us. From time to time, we may update this privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically check this Web site for updates. The most recent version of this privacy policy is reflected by the date located at the bottom of this privacy policy. Your continued use of our Web site affirms your agreement to such changes. 

Generally, you can browse through our Web site without giving us any information about yourself or your family members. When we do need personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with personal information, this privacy policy describes how we collect and use such personal information. 

#####  Disclaimer of endorsement 

References in this Web site to any third-party products, services, processes, hypertext links to third parties or other information by trade name, trademark, manufacturer, supplier or otherwise do not necessarily constitute or imply their endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation by GreatCall. Links to other sites on the World Wide Web are provided for your convenience in locating health-related information and services, and these sites are maintained by other organizations over which GreatCall exercises no control. GreatCall expressly disclaims any responsibility for the content, accuracy of the information and/or quality of the products or services provided by or advertised on these third-party web sites. 

####  Your California Privacy Rights 

Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (a) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, email and mailing address and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes and (b) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please contact us via email through our  Contact Us  page or write to us at (with a reference to California Disclosure Information): 

GreatCall, Inc.  
Attn: General Counsel  
10945 Vista Sorrento Pkwy, Suite 120  
San Diego, California 92130 

We will respond to such requests to information access within 30 days following receipt at the email or mailing address stated above. If we receive your request at a different email or mailing address, we will respond within a reasonable period of time, but not to exceed 150 days from the date received. Please note that we are only required to respond to each customer once per calendar year. 

We treat the data of everyone who comes to our site in accordance with this privacy policy, whatever their Do Not Track setting. 

#####  Information Collection 

We gather personal information needed to provide requested products or services, communicate offers on products and services that we believe will be of interest to the recipient and to administer our business. We do not collect any personal information at our Web site unless you choose to provide it to us voluntarily. We define “personal information” as information that is unique to an individual and might include a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, phone number, other contact information, title, occupation, employer, gender, date of birth, industry, personal interests, and other information when needed to provide a service requested from GreatCall. In limited circumstances, we may collect payment information such as credit card number where needed to complete a requested service or transaction. By requesting information to your mobile phone, we may obtain the following information from you: your mobile phone number, your device ID number, your carrier's name, and the date, time and content of your messages, as well as other information that you provide. We will use such information in accordance with this privacy policy. If you encounter a screen or page that requests information you do not want to share with us, do not enter the information and do not proceed with that screen or page. 

When you browse our Web site, you do so anonymously, unless you have previously indicated that you wish GreatCall to remember your login and password. We don't automatically collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our Web site you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information. Like many other web sites, GreatCall's Web site may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. Please go to "Cookies and Tracking Information" below for more information. 

GreatCall collects personal information when you register with greatcall.com for a greatcall.com client account, when you use certain GreatCall products or services, when you register to participate in an online survey, when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, or when you submit your personal information to greatcall.com for any other reason. 

From time to time, GreatCall may receive personal information from commercial vendors and partners as part of an email list purchase. GreatCall only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Policy and applicable laws. 

#####  Providing Us with Personal Information of Third Parties 

If you provide us with the personal information of another person such as your parent or your child, or direct us to share that person’s information with another person such as your sibling, you represent and warrant to GreatCall that you either (1) have full legal authority to provide such information or instructions (e.g., through power of attorney or guardianship of an elderly parent, or parental authority over a minor child), or (2) have obtained such person’s express and informed authorization to provide such information or instructions. Furthermore, when obtaining any such authorization, you must first provide him or her with a copy of this privacy policy and explain how his or her personal information will be used pursuant to this privacy policy. Periodically, you should review this privacy policy for updates and inform such third party of any such updates. By providing such person’s information or instructions to GreatCall on our Web site, you represent and warrant that you have complied with your obligations under this privacy policy. 

#####  Notice 

We will always give you the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving direct marketing, market research information or surveys. This means we assume you have given us your consent to collect and use your information in accordance with this privacy policy unless you take affirmative action to indicate that you do not consent, for instance by clicking or checking the appropriate option or box at the point of collection. In some cases, when applicable, we will provide you with the opportunity to "opt in." This means we will require your affirmative action to indicate your consent before we use your information for purposes other than the purpose for which it was submitted. 

#####  Cookies and Tracking Technology 

A cookie is a small data file that certain web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of GreatCall's Web site use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We may also employ web beacons, or site instrumentation, to monitor the behavior and visitors to our Web site and activity of our Web site, such as the number of visitors to our Web site. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our Web site information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. We also use cookies to verify the efficacy of our advertising and online marketing programs, using third party software to analyze the tracking results. The information is viewed in aggregate, meaning your personal information is not used or displayed. 

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our Web site, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of GreatCall's Web site if you do so. In particular, you may be required to accept cookies in order to complete certain actions on our Web site. You do not need to have cookies turned on, however, to use/navigate through many parts of our Web site, except access to certain of GreatCall Web site web pages may require a login and password. 

We may also employ third party service providers to place and administer such cookies and web beacons on our Web site. Such third parties may also collect your anonymized information and perform web site analytics as described in this privacy policy. We may reproduce work product created by such third parties based upon web analytics data or other similar data collected from visitors to our Web site in order to facilitate the serving of data or content in connection with providing you with more relevant advertising and content. 

#####  How We Use Collected Information 

When you visit our Web site to browse, you may choose certain online options such as (i) obtaining information about us, our products or services or third party products or services; (ii) purchasing products or services; (iii) completing our online resume form; (iv) contacting us; or (v) entering a contest or sweepstakes. When you engage in any of the foregoing activities, or use any other features or services of our Web site, you may provide us with certain personal information. We collect and store this personal information, any updates to such information that you send us, and any modifications that we make to such information. Except as set forth in this policy, we will not reveal any such personal information to any other third party without your consent, except that we may share personal information with our business associates or service providers who assist us in administering our products, services, or web sites. 

In addition, any anonymized information that you send us, such as your questions, suggestions, information, ideas, or other creative material (“Feedback”) belongs to us and will not be treated as confidential. You acknowledge and agree that we may use, reproduce, adapt, distribute, display, disclose, or create derivative works from Feedback without acknowledgement or compensation to you. 

#####  Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Your personal information is never shared outside GreatCall without your permission, except under conditions explained in this privacy policy. Inside GreatCall, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access. 

Except as set forth in this policy, we will not use, disclose, or transfer your personal information unless (1) you expressly authorize us to do so; (2) it is necessary to allow our service providers or agents to provide services for us (we will only provide those companies with the information they need to deliver the products and services, and we prohibit them from using that information for any other purpose), (3) it is necessary in order to provide products or services to you, including contacting you, emergency services and your own emergency and other specified contacts, (4) we are sending you the latest news and trends, special offers or other information we think you'd like to hear about from us (unless you have opted out of these types of communications), (5) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements, (6) it is necessary to protect the confidentiality or security of our records containing personal information, (7) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is necessary in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of GreatCall or the merger of GreatCall into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or similar transaction in which GreatCall is not the survivor, (8) it is necessary in connection with other business purposes including, without limitation, enforcing our Terms of Use, customer care, service quality, business management and operation, risk assessment, security, fraud and crime prevention/detection, monitoring, research and analysis, marketing, customer purchasing preferences and trends and dispute resolution, (9) it is necessary to comply with law enforcement, governmental mandate, or other legal requirement, if appropriate, for your protection or in connection with an investigation or prosecution of possible unlawful activity; (10) it is necessary for us to provide it to our attorneys, accountants, regulators, auditors or other advisors; or (11) it is otherwise necessary for us to disclose it as required or permitted by law. 

#####  Your Ability to Review and Delete Your Account and Information 

If you are a registered Web site user, you may request deletion of your greatcall.com account or any of your personal information held by us by contacting us via email through our  Contact Us  page. 

#####  Opting Out 

GreatCall displays retargeted ads to our Web site prospects across the Internet. We collect non‐personal information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No personal information is collected during this process. If you do not want GreatCall to collect this information, you may opt out of this service. Opting out will not in any way affect your use of our Web site. To opt‐out of retargeting, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) __.

#####  Data Security 

Your greatcall.com account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. GreatCall safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. In certain areas of our Web site, GreatCall may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. 

#####  Children and Privacy 

We are sensitive to privacy issues and look to protect your child’s information. We also strive to be fully compliant with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We strongly encourage parents and guardians to regularly monitor and supervise their children’s online activities. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 on our Web site without first obtaining verifiable consent from the child’s parent or guardian. Some of our sweepstakes will collect email addresses only without requesting the age of the entrants. All winners will be requested to provide their age. If your child under 13 is a winner, we will contact your child one time by email to request that you or your child provide by mail the information we need for prize fulfillment purposes. 

  * We do not require your child to provide more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in an activity.
  * Please also note that we do not offer activities that require the ongoing collection and use of personal information provided by children, so we will seek your permission each time we need to collect personal information from your child.
  * If you would like to review personal information about your child that we have on file, or request that certain information be changed or deleted, please send us an email through our  Contact Us  page. 

NOTICE: Visit [ www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/privacy-and-security/children's-privacy ](http://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/privacy-and-security/children%27s-privacy)__for information from the Federal Trade Commission about protecting children’s privacy online.

If a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information on our Web site without the consent of his or her parent or guardian, we ask that a parent or guardian send us an email through our  Contact Us  page, and we will delete the child’s personal information from our files. 

#####  Contests, Sweepstakes and Other Promotions 

On our Web site, you may wish to participate in contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time. Through these promotions, you may choose to participate in activities such as sharing information found on our Web site with others and sending email invitations. In connection with any contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time via our Web site, we use the information you provide to administer the contests, sweepstakes and other promotions. Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we also may use the information to communicate with you, or the other people you select, about our products and services or our partners may use such information to communicate with you about the contests, sweepstakes or other promotions or their products and services. If you choose to participate in these promotions, and are eligible to do so, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, date of birth and telephone number. 

#####  Social Media Platforms and Web sites 

Any information, communications, or material of any type or nature that you submit to our Web site (including, but not limited to any of our pages contained on a social media platform or web site such as Facebook or Twitter) by email, posting, messaging, uploading, downloading, or otherwise (collectively, a “Submission”), is done at your own risk and without any expectation of privacy. We cannot control the actions of other users of any social media platform or web site and we are therefore not responsible for any content or Submissions contained on such sites and platforms. By visiting any of our pages or web sites that are contained on a social media platform or web site, you are representing and warranting to us that you have reviewed the applicable privacy policy and terms of use of such platform or web site and that you will abide by all such provisions contained therein. 

Additionally, in the event that we offer a message board or any other interactive or social-type feature on a web site administered directly by us, please be aware that these areas may allow you to publicly post, and share with other users, certain messages, content, or other information (e.g., stories, pictures, ingredients, tips, etc.). Although we may take certain precautions to protect those who use these areas of one of our Web site, we encourage you to be wary of giving out any personal information in such public forums. The information you post can be collected and used by people you don't know. We cannot guarantee the privacy and safety of these areas and are therefore not responsible for any information you choose to post. Your use of these features is fully at your own risk. 

#####  Email 

We appreciate your questions and comments about our Web site, products and services and welcome your email messages to mailboxes listed on our Web site including emails provided to customer service. We will share your email messages with those within our organization who are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message. We may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it, but your email address and email will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. 

#####  Promotional Emails 

We may send you emails with promotional offers only if you opt-in to receiving such emails. If you would no longer like to receive emailed special event information, sales notifications or other messages from us, please send us an email through our  Contact Us  page or follow the “Unsubscribe” instructions on such emails. Your email address will be removed from our marketing list. Please allow us a reasonable period of time in order to satisfy your request, as some promotions may already be in process. 

#####  Third Party Sites 

GreatCall’s Web site contains links to other sites. GreatCall has no responsibility or liability for the actions or policies of these independent sites, do not endorse any product or service that may be mentioned or offered in such sites, and are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such sites. Our Web site may contain links to web sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with a GreatCall or GreatCall logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by GreatCall. Although we choose our business partners carefully, GreatCall is not responsible for the privacy practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site. Once you have left our Web site, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party web site to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you. 

#####  Special Statement for Job Applicants 

Any personal information you provide to us when applying for a career position with GreatCall will be used solely to consider and act upon your application. We may retain your personal information for a period of time, but only for as long as necessary for such purposes or as otherwise required by law. We may disclose your personal information to our agents for the purpose of evaluating your qualifications for the particular position you applied for, for other available positions or as otherwise required by law. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties hired by us to collect, maintain, and analyze candidates for career positions or as otherwise required by law. 

#####  Visiting our Web site from Outside of the United States 

We may store and process personal information in the United States or any other country where GreatCall, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located. If you are visiting our Web site from outside of the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States or such other countries. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using our Web site, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy. 

#####  Questions or Suggestions 

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, contact us via email through our  Contact Us  page. 

This privacy policy was last updated on July 11, 2013.
